<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?eclipse version="3.2"?>
<tips>
<!--	Tips below were reviewed on 10th of February, 2021.-->
	<tip>To execute current query use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Enter</b>.<br/>Note that queries are separated by delimiters or empty lines.</tip>
	<tip>To open query results in a new tab, use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+\</b>.<br/>Note that queries are separated by delimiters or empty lines.</tip>
	<tip>To run the current SQL script use the following shortcut: <b>Alt+X</b>.</tip>
	<tip>In order to format SQL statements use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Shift+F</b>.</tip>
	<tip>We release new version of DBeaver Community every two weeks and usually publish the updates on Mondays. You can download up-to-date version <a href="https://dbeaver.io/download">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Use the following options in SQL Editor's context menu: Execute -> Export From Query, to export data directly from SQL query without pre-executing it. </tip>
	<tip>For additional information on DBeaver features and functions, visit our <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki"> wiki page</a>.</tip>
	<tip>To open DBeaver Help contents, press <b>F1</b>.</tip>
	<tip>You can convert the selected text into uppercase using the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Shift+X</b>.</tip>
	<tip>You can convert the selected text into lowercase using the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Shift+Y</b>.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Data-Editor">Data Editor</a>, you can iterate through the view modes using the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+~</b>.</tip>
	<tip>Use <b>Ctrl+F7</b> shortcut to iterate through the view windows of DBeaver interface.</tip>
	<tip>You can turn on/off the right panels by using the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+7</b>.</tip>
	<tip>You can turn on/off the right panels by pressing <b>F7</b>.</tip>
	<tip>To refresh query results in <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/SQL-Editor">SQL Editor</a>, press <b>F5</b>.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Navigator"> Database Navigator</a>, press <b>F2</b> to rename the selected element.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Navigator"> Database Navigator</a>, press <b>F4</b> to edit properties of the selected element.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Navigator"> Database Navigator</a>, press <b>F5</b> to refresh the selected element.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Navigator"> Database Navigator</a>, press <b>Ctrl+Alt+Shift+D</b> to add the selected elements into your <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Bookmarks">bookmarks</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Use <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Bookmarks">bookmarks</a> as quick access links to objects of a database.</tip>
	<tip><a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Managing-Charts">Charts</a> let you quickly and easily turn your SELECT queries' output into a colorized bar chart.
		<br/>Note: this feature is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>To see available <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/SQL-Templates">templates</a> of SQL statements, use <b>Ctrl+Alt+Space</b> shortcut.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Data-Editor"> Data Editor</a>, press <b>Ctrl+F</b> to search for data in the current table.</tip>
	<tip>You can generate SQL statements (SELECT/INSERT/UPDATE/DELETE) based on selected rows. To generate SQL, right-click the selected rows ,then click Generate SQL and select one of the SQL commands you see.</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver allows viewing diagrams of existing tables and whole database schemas, see <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Structure-Diagrams">ER diagrams</a> article.</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver allows creating custom diagrams, see <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Custom-Diagrams">Custom Diagrams</a>.</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver is a customizable software.<br/>For additional information on optional extensions, see <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Optional-extensions"> Optional Extensions</a></tip>
	<tip>Use <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Mock-Data-Generation-in-DBeaver">DBeaver Mock Data Generator</a> when you need to create a huge quantities of realistic sample data for testing purposes and want to avoid tedious and time-consuming work of entering test data by hand.
		<br/>Note: this tool is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>To customize the menu bar and the list of menu items displayed go to Window -> Customize Perspective -> Menu Visibility tab.</tip>
	<tip>To customize the toolbar go to Window -> Customize Perspective -> Toolbar Visibility tab.</tip>
	<tip>To execute the selected SQL expression and print the results use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Alt+'</b>.</tip>
	<tip>To see the execution plan for the current query, use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Shift+E</b>.</tip>
	<tip>To execute queries of current script simultaneously and display the results in separate tabs, use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+Alt+Shift+X</b>.</tip>
	<tip>To jump to the previous query in the current SQL script, use the following shortcut: <b>Alt+Up</b>.</tip>
	<tip>To jump to the next query in the current SQL script, use the following shortcut: <b>Alt+Down</b>.</tip>
	<tip>If you are not much familiar with SQL scripting, use <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Visual-Query-Builder">Visual Query Builder</a> tool.
		<br/>Note: this tool is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>To monitor database health you can open dashboard view using main toolbar or <b>Ctrl+Alt+Shift+B</b>.
		<br/>Note: dashboards are database-specific.
	</tip>
	<tip>All the errors that occur when running SQL scripts in DBeaver, can be observed in the <a href="view://org.eclipse.pde.runtime.LogView">Error Log</a> view.<br/>The error log tracks SQL, permission and configuration errors.</tip>
	<tip>You can view queries executed in DBeaver in <a href="view://org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.queryManager">Query Manager</a> view.<br/>All the internal queries DBeaver runs to read metadata can also be found there.</tip>
	<tip>Any keyboard shortcut can be created for most of DBeaver commands. <a href="prefs://org.eclipse.ui.preferencePages.Keys">Existing shortcuts can also be changed</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can <a href="prefs://org.jkiss.dbeaver.preferences.main.sql.format">configure</a> SQL formatter globally or for a particular database.</tip>
	<tip>If you want to filter table rows by column value in <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Data-Editor">Data Editor</a>, use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+F11</b>. You can also open filter menu by pressing <b>F11</b>.</tip>
	<tip>If you want to open foreign keys menu in <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Data-Editor">Data Editor</a>, use the following shortcut: <b>Ctrl+1</b>.</tip>
	<tip>If your project requires advanced analytical tools or NoSQL database support, you can try <a href="https://dbeaver.com/">DBeaver Enterprise Edition</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can schedule your tasks to execute with specified recurrence, without needing to open DBeaver.
		<br/>Note: <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Task-Scheduler">this feature</a> is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>You can group several tasks into one composite task to easily execute a set of actions in one click.
		<br/>Note: <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Composite-Tasks">this feature</a> is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>If you're not familiar with NoSQL databases, you can use plain SQL to perform different queries.
		<br/>Note: this feature is available only in DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a>.
	</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Enterprise-Edition">Enterprise Edition</a> is fully integrated with Git version control system. You can keep your project configuration, scripts, diagrams, bookmarks and other artifacts in a Git repository.</tip>
	<tip>You can change the current commit mode and the current transaction isolation mode in the toolbar, in the dropdown menu to the right of the Commit and Rollback buttons.</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver integrates the special data viewer designed specifically for work with spatial data. You can find out more about that in our <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Working-with-Spatial-GIS-data">wiki article</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can open SQL Console with the <b>Ctrl+Alt+Enter</b> shortcut. It's great for executing a query that you don't want to save in a file.</tip>
	<tip>You can customize the representation of boolean values in Window -> Preferences -> Editors.</tip>
	<tip>If you want to only work with tables, choose Simple view in a connection context menu in <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Database-Navigator">Database Navigator</a>.</tip>
	<tip>In SQL Editor you can press Ctrl/Option+Space after asterisk in a query like "SELECT * FROM tableName" or like "INSERT INTO tableName (*)" (brackets are important) and the asterisk will be replaced with a list of all table columns.</tip>
	<tip>You can ignore the PK validation constraint when importing data into a table by selecting the Replace method in the data load settings. Supported by Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebird, and SQLite. You can find out more about that in our <a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki/Data-Import-and-Replace">wiki article</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Choose the fully qualified name of the object in the SQL Editor and use <b>Ctrl(Cmd) + Left click</b>. This will take you to the object's tab. Works with tables, columns and procedures.</tip>
<!--	Tips above were reviewed on 10th of February, 2021.-->
	<tip>If you are looking for a web-based database management tool - check our new product: <a href="https://cloudbeaver.io/">CloudBeaver</a>.</tip>
</tips>
