<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?eclipse version="3.2"?>


<!--
 * DBeaver - Universal Database Manager
 * Copyright (C) 2010-2017 Serge Rider (serge@jkiss.org)
 *
 * Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
 * you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
 * You may obtain a copy of the License at
 *
 *     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
 *
 * Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
 * distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
 * WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
 * See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
 * limitations under the License.
  -->
<tips>
	<tip>You can execute current query using <b>Ctrl+Enter</b> shortcut.<br/>
		Queries are separated by delimiters or empty lines.
	</tip>
	<tip>You can select any part of SQL script and run it with <b>Ctrl+Enter</b></tip>
	<tip>You can run SQL script using <b>Alt+X</b> shortcut. Script queries are separated with delimiters (like ";" or "go").</tip>
	<tip>You can filter table rows by column value (use <b>F11</b> or <b>Ctrl+F11</b>) or by typing SQL expression in filter edit field</tip>
	<tip>New version of DBeaver Community released once per two weeks (usually at Monday)</tip>
	<tip>You can navigate over foreign keys in data view by pressing <b>Ctrl+1</b> or using context menu.<br/>
		Back/Forward buttons (<b>Alt+Left/Right</b>) near to the filter panel allow to jump to previous tables/filter values.<br/>
		<b>Ctrl+Shift+1</b> will open links in a new editor.
	</tip>
	<tip>You can export data directly from SQL query without pre-executing it (use SQL editor context menu Execute->Export From Query).</tip>
	<tip>You can assign your own shortcuts for almost any DBeaver operations. And you can change most of existing shortcuts.</tip>
	<tip>You can debug PostgreSQL functions. Use debug tool (in the main toolbar) to initiate debug session.</tip>
	<tip>Data editor supports copy/paste of multiple cells. USe <b>Ctrl+Shift+V</b> to paste multiple rows/columns (separated by tabs and line feeds)</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver documentation can be found in our WIKI (<a href="https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki" target="_bank">https://github.com/dbeaver/dbeaver/wiki</a>)</tip>
</tips>