<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?eclipse version="3.2"?>
<tips>
	<!--        Tips below were reviewed on 28th of November 2023   -->
	<tip>DBeaver can be customized to suit your needs. Learn detailed information about optional extensions <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Optional-extensions"> here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can <a href="prefs://org.eclipse.ui.window.customizePerspective">customize the menu bar and the list of menu items displayed</a> in the <b>Menu Visibility</b> tab.</tip>
	<tip>You can <a href="prefs://org.eclipse.ui.window.customizePerspective">customize the toolbar </a> in the <b>Toolbar Visibility</b> tab.</tip>
	<tip>You can create a keyboard shortcut for most commands in DBeaver. <a href="prefs://org.eclipse.ui.preferencePages.Keys">Existing shortcuts can also be changed</a></tip>
	<tip>You can change the current <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/05/26/change-the-data-in-the-smart-way/">database transaction mode</a> in the toolbar.
		 Click the dropdown menu to the right of the <b>Commit and Rollback buttons</b>.</tip>
	<tip>If you are afraid to change the important data in the table accidentally, turn on <b>read-only mode</b> and view the table without the editing options.</tip>
	<tip>Don’t waste time editing all your connections if the password for the SSH tunnel changes.
		 Use <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/03/10/how-to-create-network-profiles/"> Network profiles</a>.</tip>
	<tip>When adding a new dependency for your driver, use Maven or Gradle scripts by switching to the <b>Dependency Declaration</b> tab.</tip>
	<tip>To securely pass external variables into DBeaver, you can use the -vars command-line parameter to specify the file containing variables.
		 Read more about Admin variables <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Admin-Variables#declare-external-variables-in-a-file"> here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can easily change a DBeaver file’s location. Just go to <b>File –> Switch Workspace</b> and set a new path.</tip>
	<tip> <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/02/keep-calm-and-use-connection-types/">Highlight your connection types</a>
		 – Test or Production – to specify their colors in your <b>Navigation Tree, Data Editor, and SQL Editor</b>.
		 This protects you from accidentally making changes to the production system.</tip>
	<tip>You can open SQL Console with the <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.sql.editor.console" showName="false"/> command. It's suitable for executing a query you don't want to save in a file.</tip>
	<tip>To execute the current query, use the command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.run.statement"/>. Please note that queries are separated by delimiters or empty lines.</tip>
	<tip>To run the current SQL script, use the command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.run.script"/>.</tip>
	<tip>In order to format SQL statements use the command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.text.content.format"/>.</tip>
	<tip>Use the following options in SQL Editor's context menu: <b>Execute -> Export From Query</b> to export data directly from SQL query without pre-executing it.</tip>
	<tip>You can convert the selected text into uppercase using the command <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.text.upperCase"/>.</tip>
	<tip>You can convert the selected text into lowercase using the <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.text.lowerCase"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To refresh query results in <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/14/your-first-queries-in-the-sql-editor/">SQL Editor</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.file.refresh"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To see available <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/SQL-Templates">templates</a> of SQL statements, use the <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.text.contentAssist.contextInformation"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>Based on selected rows, you can generate <b>SQL statements (SELECT/INSERT/UPDATE/DELETE)</b>.
		 To generate SQL, right-click the selected rows, click <b>Generate SQL</b> and select one of the SQL commands you see.</tip>
	<tip>To see the execution plan for the current query, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.run.explain"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To execute queries of the current script simultaneously and display the results in separate tabs, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.run.scriptNew"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To jump to the previous query in the current SQL script, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.query.prev"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To jump to the next query in the current SQL script, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.query.next"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>All the errors that occur when running SQL scripts in DBeaver can be observed in the <a href="view://org.eclipse.pde.runtime.LogView">Error Log</a> view.
		 The error log tracks SQL, permission, and configuration errors.</tip>
	<tip>You can view the queries executed in DBeaver in the <b>Query Manager</b>. All internal queries that DBeaver runs to read the metadata can also be found there.</tip>
	<tip>You can change the editor settings according to your personal needs. To do this, click the gear icon and go to <b>Editors -> SQL Editor</b>.
		 Here you can change the formatting, script processing settings, and more.</tip>
	<tip>In SQL Editor, you can call <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.text.contentAssist.proposals"/> after the asterisk in a query like "SELECT * FROM tableName" or
		 like "INSERT INTO tableName (*)" (brackets are important), and the asterisk will be replaced with a list of all table columns.</tip>
	<tip>Choose the fully qualified name of the object in the SQL Editor and use <b>Ctrl + Left click</b>.
		 This will take you to the object's tab. Works with tables, columns, and procedures.</tip>
	<tip>You can <b>enter an SQL expression</b> to filter the results using the Filter field above the grid.<br/>Click the expand button (<b>&#9660;</b>) on the right side to see the
		 filter history.<br/>By clicking <b>Save filter settings</b>, the filter history will be available even after restarting the app.</tip>
	<tip>You no longer need to import scripts one by one into the SQL Editor. The Import SQL Script option in DBeaver allows you
		 to select multiple files simultaneously, opening them in one editor.</tip>
	<tip>To execute the selected SQL expression and get the results, use command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.editors.sql.run.expression"/>.</tip>
	<tip>The SQL button above the <b>Navigation tree</b> allows you to open SQL scripts and change the default command.
		 For example, you can set up a quick console opening by clicking this button.</tip>
	<tip>In Data Editor, you can switch between the view modes using the command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.resultset.switchPresentation"/>.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/01/12/top-5-shortcuts-for-data-editor/">Data Editor</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.findReplace"/> command to search for data in the current table quickly.</tip>
	<tip>To filter table rows by column value in <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/01/12/top-5-shortcuts-for-data-editor/"> Data Editor,</a>
		 use the <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.resultset.filterMenu.distinct"/> command. You can also open <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.resultset.filterMenu"/>.</tip>
	<tip>To open the foreign keys menu in <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/01/12/top-5-shortcuts-for-data-editor/">Data Editor</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.jdt.ui.edit.text.java.correction.assist.proposals"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>While working with the Data Editor, you can apply to filter using the value from the clipboard.
		 Copy the value you need from any source, right-click on the cell, go to <b>Filter -> Clipboard,</b> and select the appropriate option.</tip>
	<tip>Highlighting repeated values in your data is an easy way to find them. You can enable this
		 feature by ticking the Mark occurrences of the selected cell's value checkbox here.</tip>
	<tip>You can easily change the booleans view in Properties. Click on the Gear icon, go to <b>Appearance –> Grid</b>, and click the <b>Configure booleans view</b> – Editors.
		 You can choose how your booleans will look: as icons, checkmarks, or words, for which you can set the font color.
		 In the same way, you can customize other Data editor properties, change data formatting, font size, etc.</tip>
	<tip> <a href="https://dbeaver.com/tag/colorization/">Highlight rows or filter the cells by color</a> to better view and analyze your data in a grid.
		 Apply the gradient to visualize the increase of the values in rows by size.</tip>
	<tip>If you select one or several rows in your table and click the <b>Record button</b> in the side toolbar of the editor, the rows and columns switch positions.
		 The Record mode is useful if the table contains numerous amounts of columns.</tip>
	<tip>You can enter an SQL expression to filter results using the <b>Filter field and Top toolbar</b>.
		 Your filter history is also available here. If you use DBeaver PRO, the history will be saved even after restarting the app.</tip>
	<tip>View any specific data through <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/28/the-most-convenient-way-for-data-review/">the Value panel</a> (GIS, website, images, and more).</tip>
	<tip>Using a convenient calendar, you can edit date and time fields in your tables.
		 Open <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/28/the-most-convenient-way-for-data-review/">the Value panel</a> and click on the icon with the clock
		 to switch the editor to a calendar view. You can also find a corresponding checkbox in the Preferences.</tip>
	<tip>You can turn on/off the right panels using the <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.resultset.grid.togglePreview"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>You will see a dictionary if you select the cell containing the key and
		 go to <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/28/the-most-convenient-way-for-data-review/">the Value panel</a>.It consists of Value and Description columns.
		 You can quickly view the necessary data using this table and search through it.</tip>
	<tip>If you need to count values from your table quickly, use the Grouping or Calculation panel.
		 Learn more about all opportunities of DBeaver panels <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/05/05/build-your-report-step-by-step/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can quickly view information about data format and size limits using the Metadata Panel.
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/05/19/think-about-the-content-not-about-the-structure/">The Metadata Panel</a> only works in read-only mode.
		 If you want to make changes, go to the Properties tab.</tip>
	<tip>Instead of constantly switching between all these tables to add or edit data,
		 use <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/05/19/think-about-the-content-not-about-the-structure/">the References Panel</a>.
		 It lets you quickly view which tables the selected table is associated with.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Database-Navigator">Database Navigator</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.edit.rename"/> command to rename the selected element.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Database-Navigator">Database Navigator</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.object.open"/> command to edit the selected element's properties.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Database-Navigator">Database Navigator</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.eclipse.ui.file.refresh"/> command to refresh the selected element.</tip>
	<tip>In <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Database-Navigator">Database Navigator</a>, use <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.navigator.bookmark.add"/> command to add
		 the selected elements to your <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Bookmarks">bookmarks</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Customize your Database Navigator tree to suit your needs. Learn more about Navigation tree customization
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/08/25/how-to-customize-your-navigation-tree/"> here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Choose a Simple or Advanced navigation tree view according to your needs. Learn more about how to set it up
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/08/18/simple-or-advanced-choose-your-navigation-tree-view/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>Use <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Bookmarks">bookmarks</a> as quick access links to objects of a database.</tip>
	<tip>If the Projects tab is closed, go to <b>Main menu -> Window -> Show view -> Projects</b> to open it.</tip>
	<tip>You can make your project default, and its content will be displayed in the <b>Database Navigator</b>.
		 To do this, right-click on it and choose <b>“Set Active Project."</b></tip>
	<tip>You can copy connections, bookmarks, diagrams, and scripts between your projects.</tip>
	<tip>DBeaver allows you to view diagrams for any objects: tables, views, and even entire database schemes.
		 Learn more about ER diagrams in DBeaver <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/30/two-ways-to-use-erd-in-dbeaver/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can create custom ER diagrams containing tables, relations, and notes.
		 Learn more about this feature <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/30/two-ways-to-use-erd-in-dbeaver/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>You can open the dashboard view using the <b>main toolbar</b> or command <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.ui.dashboard.open"/> to monitor database health.<br/>Note: dashboards are database-specific.</tip>
	<tip>While working on our app, you can <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/09/08/working-with-tasks-how-to-get-started/">save repetitive tasks</a>
		 such as importing and exporting data, database dumping and restoring, comparing data, etc.</tip>
	<tip>You can <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/09/22/database-tasks-view-all-your-tasks-in-one-place/">customize</a> the displayed columns in Database tasks.
		 For example, show the execution time of a particular task. To do this, you must right-click on any area of the list and go to <b>Configure columns</b>.
		 Check the appropriate boxes and <b>click OK</b>.</tip>
	<tip>You can ignore the PK validation constraint when <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Data-Import-and-Replace">importing data</a> into a
		 table by selecting the Replace method in the data load settings. Supported by Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebird, and SQLite.</tip>
	<tip>You can improve data import performance by enabling <b>Use multi-row value</b> insert in the data transfer settings.
		 Additionally, you can increase the rows count in the <b>multi-insert batch</b>.</tip>
	<tip>You can jump to a column in the result set using the <commandRef commandId="org.jkiss.dbeaver.core.resultset.grid.gotoColumn"/> command.</tip>
	<tip>To view script execution results sequentially in one tab, enable the option from the SQL Editor context menu: <b>Execute -> Toggle execution results orientation</b>.</tip>
	<tip>Would you like to use local clients in DBeaver for database backup/restore?<br/>
		<a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/Local-Client-Configuration/">Learn more about client configuring</a></tip>
	<tip>You can enable additional support of screen readers for database editors <a href="prefs://org.jkiss.dbeaver.preferences.accessibility">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip>In case you have a connection behind a proxy, you can specify the proxy setting during connection creation/editing using the <b>Network Configurations</b> button.</tip>
	<tip>If you need the high contrast theme, enable it in your operating system, and DBeaver's high contrast theme will be activated.</tip>

	<tip product="ce">DBeaver PRO is fully integrated with the
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Project-team-work/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Git version control system</a>.
		 Upgrade your DBeaver to keep your project configuration, scripts, diagrams, bookmarks, and other artifacts in a Git repository.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le,ee">With DBeaver Ultimate, you can work with databases accessible via AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure simultaneously and easily switch between their configurations.
		Learn more about how to easily work with hybrid clouds in DBeaver Ultimate
		<a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/06/01/hybrid-cloud-with-dbeaver-how-to-get-started/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">Take advantage of DBeaver PRO to <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/06/08/security-in-dbeaver-pro-questions-and-answers/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">
		 manage your data privately</a>: master password to protect all projects in the local workspace and strong credentials encryption.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,ee,ue">If you work in DBeaver with your team, choose the best way to manage user rights, restrictions, and permissions with
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/dbeaver-team-edition/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Team Edition</a>.
		 Create users and assign them convenient roles with predefined capabilities.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">If you are looking for a server-side data management solution for your team, try
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/cloudbeaver-enterprise/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">CloudBeaver</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le,ee">If you regularly work with AWS databases and need access to the files stored in the AWS, use
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/21/easy-management-for-aws-s3-files/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">the S3 browser</a> in DBeaver Ultimate.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le">Use the <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/02/10/how-does-visual-query-builder-help-optimize-your-work/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Visual
		 Query Builder</a> tool in DBeaver PRO to simplify the SQL scripting process.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">DBeaver PRO supports <a href="https://dbeaver.com/databases/?utm_source=ce&amp;tm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">all
		 popular NoSQL databases</a>: MongoDB, CouchDB, InfluxDB, and more. In addition, if you're unfamiliar with NoSQL,
		 you can use a plain SQL editor to perform different queries in DBeaver PRO.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">Get a powerful AI Assistant in DBeaver PRO to automatically create complex queries with joins.
		 Watch how it works <a href="https://youtu.be/MOaEpDa5GP0">in our tutorial video.</a>. </tip>
	<tip product="ce">In DBeaver PRO, you can quickly and easily visualize your data with
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/09/visualize-data-with-dbeaver/?utm_source=c&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Charts</a>
		 in the data grid, Panels, or result set in SQL editor.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">DBeaver PRO allows you to directly change the database schema with ERD edit mode. Learn more about database development in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/07/07/forward-engineering-with-erd/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">Get <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Mock-Data-Generation-in-DBeaver?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Mock Data Generator</a>
		 in DBeaver PRO when you need to create huge quantities of realistic sample data for testing purposes and want to avoid the tedious and time-consuming work of entering test data by hand.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">Get <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Query-Execution-Plan/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_&amp;edium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Query Execution plan</a>
		 graph mode in DBeaver PRO to view and estimate the speed of the query or script execution and to define the most expensive plan nodes.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">With DBeaver PRO, you can <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/23/import-data-with-dbeaver/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm&amp;medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">import
		 and export files</a> in any format - XLS, XLSL, XML, and more.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">In DBeaver PRO, you can get advanced options to compare data from two similar tables to navigate the differences. Learn more about Data comparison in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Data-compare?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">With DBeaver PRO, you can <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/27/how-to-use-scheduler-for-your-tasks/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">schedule
		 your tasks</a> to execute with the specified recurrence without opening DBeaver.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">With DBeaver PRO, you can group several tasks into
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/07/composite-tasks-and-how-to-create-them/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">one composite task</a>
		 to easily execute a set of actions in one click.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">In DBeaver PRO, you can create a database schema backup by using the
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Schema-compare/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Schema Compare/Migrate feature</a>
		 and save it as a task. In addition, you can execute this task automatically with Task Scheduler in DBeaver PRO.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">With DBeaver PRO, you can compare schemas, including all metadata objects, in one or different databases.
		 Learn more about the powerful schema comparison in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Schema-compare/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">To switch ER Diagram notation, right-click on a diagram, go to the <b>Notation</b> item, and select the one you need — for example, Crow's Foot.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le,ee,ue">DBeaver PRO offers a convenient way to configure Kubernetes settings for connecting to databases in a Kubernetes cluster.<br/>
		Learn more about Kubernetes configuration <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/Kubernetes-configuration/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">You can connect to almost any database by using native ODBC drivers in <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/ODBC-JDBC-Driver/">DBeaver PRO</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le,ee,ue"><a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/AI-Smart-Assistance/">AI Chat</a> in DBeaver PRO is a new way to build SQL queries automatically.
		To try it out, open the **AI Chat** tab on the right side of the SQL editor.</tip>
	<tip product="ce,le,ee,ue">You can configure DBeaver's integration with Tableau to create database connections and edit custom SQL queries conveniently.<br/>
		Learn more about Tableau integration in DBeaver PRO <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/Tableau-integration-in-DBeaver/">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ce">You can connect to a Salesforce database in DBeaver PRO using the
		<a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/Database-driver-Salesforce/">Salesforce driver</a> created by the DBeaver team.</tip>

	<tip product="le">If you are looking for a light web data manager for your team, try
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/cloudbeaver-enterprise/?utm_source=le&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">CloudBeaver Enterprise</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="le">If you are looking for a convenient collaboration tool with quick access to data without additional requests, try
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/dbeaver-team-edition/?utm_source=le&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Team Edition</a>.
		 Easily share datasets and scripts across teams in real time.</tip>
	<tip product="le,ee,ue">If you're unfamiliar with NoSQL, you can use a plain SQL editor to perform different queries.</tip>
	<tip product="le">Get a powerful AI Assistant in DBeaver Enterprise to automatically create complex queries with joins. Watch how it works
		 <a href="https://youtu.be/MOaEpDa5GP0">in our tutorial video</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="le">In DBeaver Enterprise, you can get advanced options to compare data from two similar tables to navigate the differences.
		 Learn more about Data comparison in DBeaver Enterprise <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Data-compare?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="le">With DBeaver Enterprise, you can <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/27/how-to-use-scheduler-for-your-tasks/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">schedule
		 your tasks</a> to execute with the specified recurrence without opening DBeaver.</tip>
	<tip product="le">With DBeaver Enterprise, you can group several tasks into
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/07/composite-tasks-and-how-to-create-them/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">one composite task</a>
		 to easily execute a set of actions in one click.</tip>
	<tip product="le,ee,ue">You can easily manage DBeaver's root certificates <a href="prefs://org.jkiss.dbeaver.preferences.main.truststore">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="le,ee,ue">You can connect to almost any database by using native ODBC drivers <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/ODBC-JDBC-Driver/">with the help of DBeaver ODBC</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="le,ee,ue">You can connect to a Salesforce database using the
		<a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/dbeaver/Database-driver-Salesforce/">Salesforce driver</a> created by the DBeaver team.</tip>
	<tip product="le,ee,ue">To switch ER Diagram notation, right-click on a diagram, go to the <b>Notation</b> item, and select the one you need — Crow's Foot or Bachman.</tip>

	<tip product="ee">DBeaver Enterprise is fully integrated with the <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Project-team-work/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Git
		 version control system</a>. Keep your project configuration, scripts, diagrams, bookmarks, and other artifacts in a Git repository.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">If you want a convenient data collaboration tool for your team, try
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/dbeaver-team-edition/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Team Edition</a>.
		 Easily share connections, scripts, and datasets across teams in real time. Get the full functionality of DBeaver Ultimate and CloudBeaver Enterprise.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Use the <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/02/10/how-does-visual-query-builder-help-optimize-your-work/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Visual
		 Query Builder tool</a> to simplify the SQL scripting process.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Use a powerful AI Assistant to automatically create complex queries with joins. Watch how it works <a href="https://youtu.be/MOaEpDa5GP0">in our tutorial video</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">You can quickly and easily visualize your data with
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/09/visualize-data-with-dbeaver/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Charts</a>
		 in the data grid, Panels, or result set in SQL editor.</tip>
	<tip product="ee">DBeaver Enterprise allows you to directly change the database schema with ERD edit mode. Learn more about database development in DBeaver Enterprise
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/07/07/forward-engineering-with-erd/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Use <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Mock-Data-Generation-in-DBeaver?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Mock Data Generator</a>
		 when you need to create huge quantities of realistic sample data for testing purposes and want to avoid the tedious and time-consuming work of entering test data by hand.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Use <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Query-Execution-Plan/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Query Execution plan</a>
		 graph mode to view and estimate the speed of the query or script execution and to define the most expensive plan nodes.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue"><a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/06/23/import-data-with-dbeaver/?utm_source=ce&amp;utm&amp;medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Import
		 and export files</a> in any format - XLS, XLSL, XML, and more.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Use advanced options to compare data from two similar tables to navigate the differences. Learn more about Data comparison in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Data-compare?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue"> <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/27/how-to-use-scheduler-for-your-tasks/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Schedule your tasks</a>
		 to execute with the specified recurrence without opening DBeaver.</tip>
	<tip product="ee">Group several tasks into one composite task to easily execute a set of actions in one click. Learn more about advanced task management in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/07/composite-tasks-and-how-to-create-them/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>. </tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">You can create a database schema backup by using the
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Schema-compare/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Schema Compare/Migrate feature</a>
		 and save it as a task. In addition, you can execute this task automatically with Task Scheduler.</tip>
	<tip product="ee,ue">Compare schemas, including all metadata objects, in one or different databases. Learn more about the powerful schema comparison in DBeaver PRO
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Schema-compare/?utm_source=ee&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<!--        Tips for UE   -->
	<tip product="ue">DBeaver Ultimate is fully integrated with the
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/docs/wiki/Project-team-work/?utm_source=ue&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">Git version control system</a>.
		 Keep your project configuration, scripts, diagrams, bookmarks, and other artifacts in a Git repository.</tip>
	<tip product="ue">Work with databases accessible via AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure simultaneously and easily switch between their configurations.
		 Learn more about how to easily work with hybrid clouds in DBeaver Ultimate
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2023/06/01/hybrid-cloud-with-dbeaver-how-to-get-started/?utm_source=ue&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>. </tip>
	<tip product="ue">Use the <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/04/21/easy-management-for-aws-s3-files/?utm_source=ue&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">S3 browser</a>
		 for quick access to the files stored in the AWS.</tip>
	<tip product="ue">DBeaver Ultimate allows you to directly change the database schema with ERD edit mode. Learn more about database development in DBeaver Ultimate
		 <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/07/07/forward-engineering-with-erd/?utm_source=ue&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">here</a>.</tip>
	<tip product="ue">Group several tasks into <a href="https://dbeaver.com/2022/10/07/composite-tasks-and-how-to-create-them/?utm_source=ue&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=tips">one
		 composite task</a> to easily execute a set of actions in one click.</tip>

	<tip product="te">The administrator can create an unlimited number of shared projects.</tip>
	<tip product="te">Use the admin panel to create, edit and delete shared projects.</tip>
	<tip product="te">Use the administrative panel to create, edit and delete teams.</tip>
	<tip product="te">Use the administrative panel to create, edit and delete users.</tip>
	<tip product="te">In the desktop and web versions of Team Edition, you can create connections and edit existing ones.</tip>
	<tip product="te">You can create unlimited datasets and share them with other users in real time.</tip>
	<tip product="te">You can create unlimited scripts and share them with other users in real time.</tip>
	<tip product="te">Advanced load scalability available in Team Edition.</tip>
	<tip product="te">If you want to expand the number of user roles and change the user role, please <a href="mailto:sales@dbeaver.com">get in touch</a> with our customer success team.</tip>
	<tip product="te">Use Query Manager in the web version of Team Edition to explore all users' queries.</tip>
</tips>
